Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Lateral File #1 Drawer #5
  - Alfalfa Club- DC trip-, Jan 23-25, 1975
- Lateral File #2 Drawer #1
  - Ambassadors for Tennessee
  - Ambassadors for Tennessee (for Lamar Alexander)
  - Letter to Clifford Allen, re. Proposed Financial Institution Act of, 1976
  - Annual Meeting Allied Social Science Association 12/28-30/77 NY
  - American Association of Retired Persons
  - ABA- Convention 10/19-23/85- New Orleans
  - ABA- Convention, 10/11-15/80
  - ABA- Annual Convention 10/21-25/78 Honolulu, Hawaii
  - ABA- Convention 10/15-19/77 Houston, TX
  - ABA- Convention 10/4-8/75 New York
  - American Defense Preparedness Association- Dinner for Paul Volcker 4/22/76 NY
  - American Economic Association Meeting- Atlantic City, 9/16-18/76
  - American Economic Association Meeting- Dallas, 12/27-28/75
  - American Economic Association Meeting- San Francisco 12/27-30/74- 87th Annual American Management Association- Financial Council
  - Mary Anderson
  - The Atlantic Council
  - Memo to Earthman, (7/10/80)
  - Avis Memo on Automotive Import Restriction and Depreciation
  - Steve Axilrod Reception-, DC 7/10-11/86
  - Bald Peak Economic Conference- 10/12-14/87 Melvin Village, NH
  - Bald Peak Economic Conference- 10/12-14/87 Melvin Village, NH
  - Baker Initiative (IPC Member Letters)
  - Bald Peak 1983 Info
  - Bank Julius Baer and Co, LTD
  - Bankers’ Association for Foreign Trade- The Greenbrier 4/6-10/75 White Sulpher Springs, WV
  - BAFT Convention 5/1-5/77 Puerto Rico
  - BAFT 56th Annual Meeting 5/14-18/78- The Homestead Hot Springs, VA
  - Bankers’ Association for Foreign Trade (General Info)
  - Bankers’ Association for Foreign Trade (General Info)
  - BAFT- Convention, 5/31-6/4/81
  - BAFT- Annual Meeting, 4/25-29/82
  - BAFT- Annual Meeting Dorado, Puerto Rico, 4/10-14/83
  - BAFT- Annual Meeting Dorado, Puerto Rico, 4/10-14/83
  - BAFT-62nd Annual Meeting Coronado, CA, 4/8-12/84
  - BAFT- Boca Raton Florida, 5/12-16/85
  - BAFT- Phoenix, Arizona, 5/15-19/86
  - BAFT- Boca Raton, Florida 4/26-30/87 (Bettie’s)
  - Bank for International Settlements- General Correspondence
  - Bank for International Settlements- Information, 1981
  - Bank for International Settlements- BIS
  - Bank for International Settlements- Annual Report, June 12, 1978
  - IMF/IBRD Meeting in Manila week of, October 4, 1976
  - IMF, 1979
  - Bank and Funds Meeting, DC-, 8/31-9/6/75
  - Bank and Funds Meeting, DC-, 9/30-10/4/74
  - Terry Bart’s Noon Show Interview, 4/16/75
  - Wisconsin Graduate School of Banking- Section Leaders Meeting Chicago, 2/26/76
  - Wisconsin Graduate School of Banking-, Aug 10-16, 1975
  - University of Wisconsin Madison- International Finance Course 1975 Session, Mar 18
  - Wisconsin Graduate School of Banking-, Aug 15-21, 1976
  - University of Wisconsin- 1982 Session (Herbert V. Prochnow Graduate School)
  - Wisconsin Graduate School of Banking- 1981 Session
  - Wisconsin Graduate School of Banking-, Aug 13-19, 1978
  - Wisconsin Graduate School of Banking-, Aug 1977
  - Snowden Village Associates, L.P., Aug 23, 1985
  - Expandable File- Sovran Benefits
- Lateral File #2 Drawer #2
  - Automobile
  - Avantor Financial Corporation “A” Correspondence
  - Ad Hoc – Special Joint Board of Directors Meeting 3/22/88 9:30 am
  - Ad Hoc Committee June 1987 75th Alfalfa Club Dinner 1/30/88 (Workfile)
  - American Airlines (Don P. O’Hare) Exchange Club-, 9/12/89
  - American Academy of Achievement- 7/2/88 Opryland USA INC Banquet, Golden Plate Dave Anderson
  - Letters and Memos from Denny Bottorff to JDD
  - Bios (on Different Individuals)
  - Sovran- Media Kit
  - Bottorff Project on World Bank
  - Bottorff Report to Atlanta Fed 2/12/88 (Daane and West)
  - Bottorff- Monitoring Regional Economic Condition
  - Bottorff- Monthly Economic Report, 2/4/88
  - Bottorff- Monthly Economic Reports 1987 1990- Bretton Woods
  - The Bretton Woods Committee (Contributors) 1987 Memo
  - Todd Bottorff- Meeting 5/27/87 10:30 am
  - Business cards from Trips, 1986
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1987
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1987
  - Correspondence, 1989
  - Misc. Correspondence
  - JDD- Speaking at Clark University- June 14-15, 1990 Boston, Bob Ulrich
  - Data Resources, Ins (DRI)
  - Deloitte
  - William B. Dale’s Paper on World Bank Debt Strategy and GCI
  - William B. Dale’s Bio and Correspondence
  - The Cumberland Club
  - Meeting- 1989 Deposit and Loan Growth Rates 7/14/88 11 am
  - - Directors Questionnaire (for 1987), 1986
  - - Directors Questionnaire, 1985
  - - Directors Questionnaire, 1984
  - Jan 1983- CUC Directors Questionnaire- Officers and Directors
  - Discount Corporation of America- Annual Outing at Piping Rock Club Locust Valley, NY, May 23, 1989
  - Center of Excellence in Banking- ETSU
  - The Exchange Club of Nashville
  - European Trip-, June 1983
  - Essentials of Banking Seminar- Daane Work File
  - Expense Requests- Data Resources (DRI), 1989
  - Data Resources (DRI) Expenses, 1988
  - Expenses/ Sovran 1990- Expense- NFA, 1990
  - - NFA Expense Requests, 1989
  - Sovran Bank/ Central South Expenses 1988 1988- NFA Expenses
  - Clippings
  - Chicago Board of Trade Information
  - Cards- (Travel, Charge, Etc.) Clubs
  - - 55th Central High School Reunion- Jun 15-17, 1990
  - - Central High School Reunion, 1989; 6/23/89
  - China (Dishes)
  - Clock
  - Code of Conduct- Sovran- 1989 1989 Whittaker Corp.- Expense Requests 1988 Whittaker Corp.- Expense Requests 1989 Expense Requests Sovran Bank
  - Fax 3rd Floor
  - Directors Dinner and Reception- FRB Atlanta, 9/7/89
  - Foreign Contracts
  - Fed Reserve Banks and Board of Governors- Misc. Information
  - FRB Chicago- Conference on Bank Structure and Competition- May 1-3, 1985 FRB Chicago- Conference on Bank Structure and Competition
  - Financial Market Reports
  - Luncheon- Malcolm S. Forbes, Jr.- Vanderbilt Plaza 12noon, 9/18/85
  - Four Seasons Reimbursement File
  - Fruit Companies
  - The Cumberland Club- 26th Floor- Southvest LBO Fund, L.P. Advisory Committee Meeting 3/29/90 2 pm
  - Gen Cap America, Inc (Andrew Byrd) Meeting Cumberland Club 5 pm
  - The U. Club- High Level Economic Conference 4/26/90 11:45- 1:30
  - The U. Club- Genesco High Level Economic Conference 11/2/89 11:15 am Genesco High Level Economic Conference 4/27/89 11:15 am
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 11/3/88/ 11:15-1:30
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 4/28/88 Meeting
  - Gannett Co.
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 11/5/87 39th Genesco High Level Economic Conference 4/23/87 U.Club
  - Halliburton
  - Bridget Blaise 1990 MBA Recommendations
  - Harvard Recommendations (Candidates), Dec 1989
  - Pat Harrison 1987 Interoffice Memos and Reports “I “ Correspondence
  - International Symposium on Banking and Payment Services Jun 7-9, 1989 D.C. Interoffice Correspondence 1987 1986 Report- International Monetary Conference- Boston
  - The Industrial Bank of Japan, LTD Atlanta, 1/11/88
  - “J” Correspondence 1989- Jackson Hole, Wyo Aug
  - Japan
  - Japanese Ceravan-, 4/25/83
  - April 1, 1988- Breakfast- Manuel Johnson- Bank Dining Room “K” Correspondence
  - Kyowa Bank, LTD “L” Correspondence
  - Les Ambassaduers Club
  - Lists Names
  - Loan Officers Handbook (William J. Korsuik) Editorial Advisory Board London Trip- International Club of Vanderbilt, 3/5-13/88
  - Los Angeles Trip File (Information for Area) “M” Correspondence
  - Matching Gifts Program (From Whittakers)
  - Memphis Club- Board of Directors 11/14/86- Class Panel Member for Management Associates 1989- Mexico- 1989-1992 Financing Package
  - Mercedes Benz Club of America, Inc.
  - London England- George Moore Birthday Party, 4/1/85
- Lateral File #2 Drawer #3
  - N Correspondence
  - NABE- National Association of Business Economists
  - NFA-, 1989
  - NFA-, 1989
  - The Nashville Banner- Board of Contributors 1983- General File
  - NFA- Daane’s Directorship, 1987
  - P Correspondence
  - Oil Recovery Corporation of America (ORCA) Meeting of the Board 9/2/86 ORCA- Oil Recovery Corporation of America
  - Organizational Charts
  - The Overseas Bankers Club, London England
  - Paris- Restaurant List
  - PAC (Sovran), 1989
  - Patterson School Board of Advisors- Correspondence
  - Patterson School Board of Advisors- Lexington, KY Oct 8-11, 1987 Patterson School
  - Patterson School Brochures
  - Photographs
  - Personal- Envelope
  - Memos- Jim Rainey 1988 Thru
  - Jim Rainey Memos, 1989
  - Questionnaires- Whittaker 12/9/87 and 1988 1987 Proxy Statement 1986 Proxy Statement
  - Press
  - Questionnaire- Sovran, 1987, 1988, 1990
  - Relationship Management Board Room, Jan 24, 1989
  - Relationship Management
  - Resumes, 1989
  - Ms. Bronwyn D. Andreas (Resume File)
  - Arden Nagler (Resumes and Letters)
  - Resumes
  - Retreat- 1985 (Fall Business Planning Process 1986) Fairfield Glade
  - Robertson Association 1990 United Way Planning Retreat- Fairfield Glade 6/18-20/87 Roundtable File 2989
  - Roundtable File, 1987-1988
  - Roundtable File, 1989-1990
  - Roundtable Membership File
  - R Correspondence
  - S Correspondence L. William Seidman Letters, 1990
  - Bob Shell Memos, 1989
  - SBU Communications Meeting-, 9/12/89
  - Shirts
  - Silverware
  - The Sovran Celebration- A Salute to Customers- Overview Meeting, 8/8/89
  - Sovran Fest- 8/5/89 Richmond, VA
  - Southvest LBO Fund L.P.- Gen Cap America, INC.
  - Southvest LBO Fund L.P.- 3/14/89- Chairman Daane
  - Joint Board of Directors Meeting, 9/12/89
  - Steeplechase Iroquois
  - St. George’s Episcopal Church 3/15/90 Presentation of Alex Heard
  - St. George’s Episcopal Church
  - Swan Ball- Awards, 1990
  - Swan Ball File #2, 1988
  - Swan Awards, 1989
  - Swan Ball, 1983
  - Swan Ball, 1987
  - Swan Ball, 1986
  - Swan Ball 6/8/85, 1985
  - Swan Awards File #2, 1989
  - Swan Ball, 1984
  - Telephone System at Daane’s Home
  - Commerce Union- Telephone
  - Telephone Log
  - Task Force on Financial Service Industry (State of Tennessee
  - Task Force Committee Meeting, 9/1/82
  - Telephone Call Logs (Blank)
  - Trust Letter (By Mr. Daane for Presentation to SB/CS Executive Committee 2/22/89 Trust Board Meeting-, 10/26/88
  - July 26th Trust Board Meeting
  - Toyota
  - TSCPA Speech, 1983
  - Travel- Airports, Maps, Etc. 1989- OGSM- Vanderbilt- Retirement Conference-, April 13-14
  - Spring 1989 VU Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy
  - Spring 1988 VU Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy
  - Seminar Expenses, 1988
  - Vanderbilt Seminar Expenses (Belle Meade Country Club and Tulip Tree), 1986
  - Vanderbilt Seminar Expenses, 1987
  - Vanderbilt Seminar Expenses, 1987
  - V.U. Correspondence
  - W Correspondence
  - Whittaker Special Board Meeting, L.A. 1/27/89 1989 Whittaker
  - WLAC- Ruth Ann Leech Talk Show, 8/23/83
  - Wine
  - Remarks to Wednesday Club- Danville, Virginia, 3/9/88
  - Volker- D.C. Trip (Rivlin and Penner), 9/13-15/83
  - X-Y-Z Correspondence
  - Properties Evaluations (From Jacques- Miller), 1988
  - Tax Info, 1977
  - Tax Info, 1979
  - Income Tax Return, 1979
  - Tax Return, 1980
  - Income Tax Info, 1980
  - Tax Info, 1981
  - Tax Year Ended 12/31/81
  - Tax Returns, 1974
  - Tax Returns, 1975
  - Taxes, 1976
  - Tax Return, 1978
  - Tax Info, 1978
  - Virginia Income Tax, 1969
  - AT&T Stock, 1984
  - Securities
  - Continental Group- Stock
  - File Lists from JDD (Move from 3rd to 1st-, Feb 1989)
  - Record of Files- JDD Pre-, 1974
  - File Lists
  - CUB Chattanooga- Loan [Paid]
  - CUB Note [Paid]
  - First American National Bank Loan [Paid]
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.
  - Nashville City Bank Loan [Paid]
  - Prime and Investment Payments- Third National Bank Loan [Paid] United American Bank of Nashville Loan [Paid]
  - Income Tax Info, 1982
  - Regency Park Associate, LTD. (Partnership with Jacques Miller) [Sold]
  - Investment Properties
  - and 1985 Chowning Investments, LTD., 1984
  - Fontaine Village Investment [Sold]
- Lateral File #2 Drawer # 4
  - Banner Business Profiles Award Dinner 5/22/86 at CUB
  - Geoffrey L. Bell- J. Henry Schroder Wagg and Co. Limited
  - For Daane from Wayne Robbins
  - Belmont College- Board of Associates
  - Belmont Crockroft Forum Banquet, 2/13/84
  - Belle Meade Country Club Info, 1983
  - Bretton Woods Committee Annual Meeting 3/10/89- D.C.
  - C.B.O.T. Special Committee on International Expansion, 12/17/81
  - CTC- Commerce Trading Corporation
  - Correspondence File- Incoming and Outgoing, 1986
  - Correspondence File, 1985
  - Correspondence, 1985
  - Discount Corporation Meeting
  - Discount Corporation of New York
  - Discount Corporation of America- Piping Rock Club 5/20/86 Dogs
  - Mitch Draizin
  - Professor Gunster Dufey- University of Michigan
  - Duke University
  - Elvin A. Duerst, 1986
  - Elvin A. Duerst (Paintings, 1986)
  - Elvin A. Duerst Bio Information
  - Export Policy
  - Exercises
  - Diesel Sales and Services, Inc. Board Meeting, 4/30/90
  - DSS Business Overview, 1990
  - DSS Co., Inc.- Board, 12/11/89
  - DSS Board Meeting, 8/10/89, 8/11/89
  - DSS Board Meeting, 4/20/89
  - DSS Board of Directors Meeting, 12/14/88
  - DSS Board Meeting, 3/29/88
  - DSS Board Meeting, 12/6/87
  - DSS, Inc.
  - DSS Board Meeting, 11/8/85
  - DSS Board of Directors Meeting, 3/27/86
  - DSS Board of Directors Meeting, 3/25/85
  - DSS Board of Directors Meeting, 1/16/86
  - DSS Board of Directors Meeting, 7/16/85
  - DSS Board of Directors Meeting, 9/18/86
  - Data Resources
  - Data Resources- DRI- US Economic Conference NY, 10/6/87
  - Data Resources- DRI- US Economic Outlook Conference Chicago, 12/10/87
  - DRI- US Economic Conference NYC, 10/6/87
  - Debt Busters (Tennessee Municipal League), 9/11/86
  - JDD- Checking Account 1982 Deposits and Debits
  - Depository Institutions Amendments of 1982 (Summary)
  - Tom Earthman
  - EBIC Investments in TVB
  - Edge Acts
  - EMB Ltd. Research Economists
  - Euromoney Article- Oct, 1977
  - Article for Euromoney, Submitted, 4/11/77
  - Speech- Exchange Club of Nashville, 12/10/75
  - CSHA Workshop- Council on State Housing Agency-, 10/15/84
  - Canal Treaties- Committee of Americas for the Canal Treaties
  - Capital Tracing
  - Celebrity Speakers Bureau
  - G 10 Central Banks- Official Rosters
  - Samuel B. Chase, Jr. Nashville Visit, 4/21/75
  - Chattanooga Visit, 1/22/76
  - Banco de Chile
  - China 1976 Business Christmas Cards
  - Cisneros Transactions
  - William B. Cockroft Forum (Info-, 1986)
  - William B. Cockroft Forum CUB- Charitable Contributions
  - Commerce Trading Corporation, 5/20/85
  - DSS 1989 Business Plan
  - Belle Meade Country Club
  - The Coop (Club)
  - Cumberland Club
  - Diners Club
  - Exchange Club
  - Hermitage Country Club
  - Conference on Bank Structure and Competition, Chicago, 5/9-11/90
  - University Club
  - Conference on Bank Structure and Competition, Chicago-, 4/24-25/84
  - Speech- Conference Board Annual Outlook Conference NY, 9/15/76
  - The Conference Board – NY Sep 1984 (Notes)
  - Conference Board Annual Business Outlook Confernece, NY 9/15/76 Conference of Christians and Jews, 1976 and 1977
  - Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 6/9/86
  - CBO- Panel of Economic Advidors- D.C., 6/24/85
  - CBO Meeting D.C., 12/20/82
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors- D.C., 9/24-25/75
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors- D.C., 9/24-25/75
  - COMU- PAC CUB Good Government Committee
  - Cook Industries
  - Cooper Clinic Reports
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors-, 6/27-28/76
  - CBO Board of Advisors Meeting –, 11/18-20/76
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting- D.C., 1/5/78
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting- D.C. 6/26/78
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting- D.C. 12/78
  - CBO Advisory Meeting- 2/6/79
  - CBO- Panel- DRI Reference Materials
  - CBO Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting- D.C., 2/5-7/76
  - Cooper Clinic- Dallas, 9/14/88
  - Cooper Clinic- Dallas, 9/11/86
  - Cooper Clinic- Dallas, 9/11/85
  - Cooper Clinic- Dallas, 8/29/83
  - Cooper Clinic- Dallas, 9/11/84
  - Cooper Clinic-, 1983
  - Cooper Clinic- Dallas, 9/10/87
  - Correspondence, 1987
  - Correspondence, 1986
  - Correspondence “Brochure Type”, 1985-1986
- Lateral File #2 Drawer #5
  - Cottage Account Bank File- Michigan
  - FRB Atlanta- (R. Dornbusch Lecture) Sep 25, 1987
  - FRB Atlanta-, Sep 25, 1987
  - FRB Atlanta- Dinner for Gov. H. Robert Heller, 2/12/87
  - FRB Atlanta- Reception- Andrew F. Brimmer, 6/13/85
  - FRB Atlanta- 1/10/85- Dinner
  - FRB Atlanta- Reception/Dinner, 7/12/84
  - FRB Atlanta- Reception, MacLaury, 1/12/84
  - FDIC News Releases
  - Federal Bank Supervision- Senate Bills 684 and 711 (R.C. Holland) CED Federal Banking Agency Audit Act H.R. 2176
  - Federal Reserve Press Releases
  - Federal Reserve
  - Federal Reserve Board Chairman G. William Miller (Pending- Chairman) Recommendation to Federal Reserve Board of Governors, 1978
  - FOMC
  - Foreign Direct Investments
  - Foreign Exchange Policy Committee, 11/6/78
  - Four Seasons Travel Invoices- Paid
  - Richard H. Fulton
  - Hon. Evan Galbraith- U.S. Ambassador to France (News Clippings)
  - Genesco Retirement Trust Fund (General Info)
  - Genesco Retirement Trust Fund Meeting, 10/25/82
  - Genesco Retirement Trust Fund Meeting, 7/26/82
  - M.S. Wiggington- Genesco
  - Genesco Meeting (Gesco) With M. Wiggington, 7/23/84
  - Genesco Meeting (Gesco), 5/21/84
  - Genesco Retirement Trust Meeting with Matt Wiggington 3/26/84 Genesco Meeting, 12/21/83
  - Genesco Master Pension Trust
  - Genesco Retirement Committee- Quarterly Meeting, 10/22/84
  - Genesco Luncheon Meeting, 1/22/85
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 11/14/74 (M.S. Wiggington) Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 5/1/75
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 10/1/75
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/22/82
  - Reception to Honor Matt Wiggington, 12/23/86
  - Genesco Inc (Wiggington)
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 11/2/79
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/29/76
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 10/21/76
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/28/77
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 10/3/77 U. Club
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 11/3/77
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/27/78
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 10/25/84
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/28/83
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 11/3/83
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 11/11/82
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 10/23/80
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/24/80
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/23/81
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 11/5/81
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 10/26/78
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/26/79
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 5/3/84
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/25/85
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference 10/31/85 U.Club
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 4/24/86
  - Genesco High Level Economic Conference, 11/6/86
  - General Capital Corporation
  - Georgetown University Bankers Forum- D.C., 11/1/85
  - Georgetown Public Forum 9/5/75
  - Georgetown University Bankers Conference- D.C., 11/14/79
  - Georgetown University Bankers Conference- D.C., 11/19/76
  - Gold, 1974
  - Gold, 1975
  - Golembe Associates Inc.- Correspondence
  - Gramm- Rudman Notes, Jan 1986
  - Greater Nashville 100 Luncheon- 11/13/86 (CUB and Arthur Andersen Co.) HCA
  - James F. Hamilton
  - Hamilton Bank of Chattanooga R. B. Harkness- St. Thomas
  - Harpeth Hall Men’s Club 350th Harvard Celebration- Boston 9/3-7/86 Bettie’s File Harvard University- JFK School of Government-, DC 3/27/83
  - Harvard Alumni Presidential Appointee Reception, 2/11/82
  - Harvard Club of Nashville and Middle Tennessee
  - Harvard Graduate Society (Boston Mass)
  - Harvard Graduate Society Meeting-, DC 3/14-15/79
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council Meeting- Boston, 5/1-2/75
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council Meeting- Boston, 10/2-4/75
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council Meeting- Boston, 2/20/76
  - Sir John and Lady Hicks (Biographical Info)
  - Olveta Clup Hobby
  - Jasper Q. Hollow
  - Jack Horrigan
  - HCA
  - HCA Lunch (Remarks by Henry Kaufman), 4/15/83
  - House Banking, Currency and Housing Committee HR 212 Bill
  - Dock Houk
  - Mrs. Frank K. Houston (Correspondence- JD)
  - IMF/World Bank Meeting- DC 1989 Bettie’s Work File
  - IMF/World Bank-, DC 9/29-10/1/87
  - IMF/World Bank Meetings-, DC 1986
  - IMF/World Bank Meeting- West Berlin, Germany, 1988
  - IMF/World Bank Briefing Book-, DC 1983
  - IMF/World Bank Briefing Book- Toronto, Canada, 1982
  - IMF Invitations- Chronological Order and Copy of Jack F. Matlock Letter
  - IMF/World Bank- Clippings, 1987
  - IMF/World Bank- Clippings, 1986
  - IMF- General Correspondence
  - IMF/World Bank Meetings- Seoul Korea 1985 1985- IMF and Japan/S.E. Clippings
  - IMF- Seoul, Korea-, 10/8-11/85
  - IMF 1984 Misc.
  - IMF/World Bank Meeting- DC Sept, 1983
  - Delegation List and Special Guest List- Bank and Fund Meeting
  - Bank and Fund Meeting-, DC 9/26-28/77
    - -Provisional Schedule of Meetings, Bank and Fund Meeting
    - -Target Calls for Bank and Fund
    - - Hotel and Meeting Registration Info, bank and Fund Meeting
  - Bank and Fund Meeting- D.C., 9/25-28/78
  - Official Delegate and guest List
  - Cocktail party invitation List
  - Bank and Fund Meetings- D.C. 9/25-28/78- Invitations to JDD
  - Target Calls
  - TVB/CUB- IMF/ IBRD Cocktail Party Guest List- Acceptances and Regrets- Extra Invitations Inside Bank and Fund Invitations Accepted by JDD Plus Daily 305 Cards and One Page sheet Outlining Activities Bank and Fund- Misc. Names and Addresses
  - IMF- World Bank-, DC 9/27-30/83
    - -Board of Governors Annual Reports
    - -IMF Clippings
    - -Georgetown University Bankers Forum-, DC Sept 26, 1983
    - -IMF Telephone Directory
  - IMF/World Bank-, Sept 1984
    - -IMF/World Bank Briefing Book, 1984
    - -Board of Governors Annual Reports
    - -IMF- Invitations Received for JDD
    - -1984 IMF- Lists (U.S. and International) (Changes and Final Lists)
  - Bankers Forum- Georgetown University- DC 9/22/84 1985- IMF Invitations Received by JDD
  - Bank of Spain
  - International Financial Conference- General Correspondence Investment Management Policies
  - Invitations
  - Iran Crisis, 1979
  - Itineraries, 1979
  - JDD, IMF Meetings- Manila, Oct 1976
  - IMF
- Lateral Case #3 Drawer #1
  - American Airlines- Senior Savers Info, 1986
  - Eastern Airlines Frequent Traveler Bonus Program
  - Northwest
  - Delta Airlines Frequent Traveler Program
  - Delta Airlines- Western Airlines- Merged with Delta April1987 American AAdvantage-, 1988-1990
  - Mrs. Barbara Daane- 1987- American AAdvantage FF Mileage TWA Frequent Flyer
  - Pan Am Airlines Frequent Traveler System
  - United
  - Northwest and Republic Airlines Frequent Flyer
  - U S Air Frequent Flyer
  - Itineraries-, 1990
  - Itineraries-, 1989
  - Itineraries-, 1988
  - Itineraries-, 1987
  - Itineraries-, 1986
  - Itineraries-, 1985
  - Itineraries-, 1984
  - Itineraries-, 1983
  - Itineraries-, 1982
  - Itineraries-, 1981
  - Commerce Union Corporation- Blank Expense Reports
  - Blank Insurance Forms (Medical and Dental), 1988
  - “New” Dental Forms (Provident Ins.), 1989
  - “New” Health Insurance Forms (Metropolitan Insurance Co.) Olivia Daane- Dental, 1989
  - Dewey Daane- Dental
  - Olivia Daane- Insurance
  - Whitney Daane- Insurance
  - Barbara Daane- Insurance J. Dewey Daane- Insurance
  - Feb. 1987- Dental/Surgery- Olivia Daane Blue Cross/Blue Shield Insurance
    - Daane- Medical Information
    - Daane- Insurance
    - JDD’s Insurance “Finished”
    - Old Dental Insurance
  - Medical Insurance
  - Medical Information, 1990